Contact

abhishek.ece1993@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/abhishek-paul-621281141 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

AngularJS

Javascript

Core Java

Languages

Hindi (Professional Working)
Bengali (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)

Certifications

IBM Agile Explorer
IBM Carbon Design System
Developer Essentials - React

Honors-Awards

Infosys Insta Award

Abhishek Paul

Software Developer - Watson IOT, IBM India Kolkata

Summary

Experienced System Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in angularjs, nodejs, JavaScript, css3, html5, jQuery,PostgreSQL, SQL, Underscore.js, lodash, Automation Testing, unit testing etc. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.) focused in Electronics & Communication from St. Thomas' College of Engineering & Technology 122.

Experience

IBM

Software Developer March 2019 - Present (1 year 6 months)

Infosys

Bangalore

2 years 8 months

Senior System Engineer October 2018 - March 2019 (6 months) Bangalore

System Engineer

August 2016 - October 2018 (2 years 3 months)

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Education

St. Thomas' College of Engineering & Technology 122
Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Electronics & Communication
· (2012 - 2016)

Madhyamgram High School

Higher secondary, science · (2010 - 2012)

Madhyamgram High school secondary, general study · (2005 - 2010)